https://www.123mc.com/en/privacy-policy/

CloseLog inLog-InLog-InCloseWhy Mission Managed SCADABackSimply More IntelligentOptimized for Your IndustryData ProtectionGuaranteed Price StabilityContinuous Updates/UpgradesMission ServicesNotificationsWeb-based InterfaceReportsTechnical SupportProductsBackReal-Time Alarm SystemsMyDro 150, 850Legacy M110, M800Manhole MonitorSoftware OptionsTank and WellOPC-UAAnalog and Digital InterconnectUpgradesHardware AccessoriesAntennas and AccessoriesExpansion Boards and ModulesManhole Monitor HardwarePower Accessories and ComponentsReplacement and Component PartsTransducers and InstrumentationRainfall AccessoriesSolar OptionsOur ServicesSolutionsBackBy ApplicationLift StationTank and WellRainfall MonitoringCSO/SSOOPC-UACase StudiesWaterWastewaterHybrid SCADAOtherSupportBackLiteratureVideosWebinarsNewsletterUpcoming Trade ShowsAbout UsBackCompany OverviewCareer OpportunitiesMission Instrumentation Partner ProgramPrivacy PolicyContact UsMission Communications guarantees that it will never, under any circumstances, sell, trade, or make public a customer’s personal information unless they designate otherwise. All personal information provided will remain confidential. In addition, customers will always have the option to edit the information provided or have their personal information removed from Mission records.Traffic DataWhen customers visit 123mc.com, or 123SCADA.com the system logs basic information about their computers, including: IP address, operating system (e.g., Windows 10, OSX), browser software (e.g., Chrome, FireFox, Microsoft Internet Explorer), and Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast). Mission also collects information about what is viewed on the site. This information reflects customers as a whole and is used to help the company better understand the information that is of most interest.Use of CookiesMission Communications employs cookies—small text files placed on the hard drive of customer computers—to track the screen size (800×600, 1024×768, etc.) selected for that particular computer, and the length of time a user spends on the 123mc.com site. Cookies also help diagnose problems with the server. For more information regarding cookies, please click here.Notification Email AddressesAfter signing up online, users receive site alerts and management reports emailed from 123mc.com. Mission does not share addresses with other companies or partners. Mission does not use these addresses for marketing purposes. They are only used for system notifications.RecordingsMission records voice initiated alarm notifications for reporting and audit trail purposes.Location DataMission tracks and records user location by latitude longitude when the user grants access.Linking to Other Sites123mc.com contains links to other sites, such as news and weather. Mission is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.Copyrights and TrademarksAll external trademarks herein belong to their respective owners. Third party brands, product names, trade names, corporate names, and company names mentioned may be trademarks of their respective owners or registered trademarks of other companies and are used for purposes of explanation and to the owner’s benefit, without implying a violation of copyright law.Other Disclosure of Personal InformationMission Communications will not use or disclose personal information without consent, except (i) as described in this privacy policy or (ii) as required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority.Contacting Mission CommunicationsContact Mission representatives with questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or personal dealings with this website using the information below:Mission Communications, LLC
3170 Reps Miller Rd
Suite 190
Norcross, GA 300711-877-993-1911 – Toll-Free1-678-969-0021 – Office1-678-969-0541 – Faxsales@123mc.comtechsupport@123mc.comMission Communications reserves the right to amend this Privacy Statement at any time, without notice, and only the current Privacy Statement may be deemed effective.
